[Music]
you're listening to the AI native Dev
brought to you by
Tesla hello everyone welcome back to the
AI native Dev on the show today we have
Dez trainer who is the co-founder of
intercom who are one of the earliest
companies to really properly Embrace AI
so we'll hear a lot about those types of
learnings and this is also an active
angel investor so we'll have interesting
perspectives about AI for things beyond
the intercom sphere so thanks for coming
on to the show do thanks for having me
guy excited we're going to talk a lot
about autonomy of AI and testing and
learnings but I think people need a bit
more context if they're not familiar
with with intercom and specifically with
Finn with your AI
agent sure I mean intercom we started
Life as a sort of general purpose
customer communication tools so like a
way that internet businesses could talk
to their customers and vice versa I'll
skip to 10 years in between but let's
just say two years ago we went all in on
customer support and two I guess maybe
four weeks later chat GPT launched and
then AI first customer support became
the most obvious sort of future of what
it meant to build out customer service
so we jumped on that basically I think
chat GPT dropped November 30th this by
December 1st we were working on what
would be like the sort of future of our
platform and the huge components of that
was AI native features and then later on
Finn and then more recently Finn
co-pilot but we're basically taking an
AI first approach to to building out a
support platform because we think that's
obviously where the future of basically
every industry but certainly customer
service yeah no super interesting and I
think I guess I think of intercom
oftentimes as the one that pioneered or
at least popularized the the sort of
chat-based support that is in line
typically bottom right corner little
speak bubble speech bubble on websites
so I guess you were very it felt
relatively natural as chat product to to
embrace it like chat GPT felt
reminiscent or felt familiar yeah
exactly right like I think chat Bots are
what happened when two Mega Trends one
was like the rise of messaging and the
other one was like the rise of AI
combined and in chatbot B had multiple
false starts like you probably remember
the if this then that Bots um and then
like they slightly matured and matured
again but realistically generative AI is
the thing that made them like not [ __ ]
which is where the industry needed to
get to but I think yeah like we we were
like certainly foundational on
pioneering and moving support to being
an always on thing so you could
literally talk to the people behind a
tesle or a sneak or whatever just by
engaging in the bottom right hand corner
and ask a question and get a quick
answer the you know and like that was
for the longest time that was rcom's
hundreds of millions of Revenue came
from and then obviously how does the
world change when those answers can be
quite damn good and generated in zero
seconds by an autonomous agent that can
find out answers and see what's been
said before and disambiguate and qualify
and follow up and all sorts of stuff
like that the nature of it all changes
and that's what we've been like
wrestling with since basically every day
since yeah yeah super interesting so
we'll dig into those but I think maybe
to to give us a bit of a chronological
order maybe you you had you spoke in
various podcasts on this sort of Code
Red moment of hey we we see this you had
if I remember correctly fergo your head
of AI saw chat B got you all looking
into it and you all agreed that you
shouldn't increment hey let's put three
people on it but rather route a bunch of
people into this and really bet on this
approach I think what I find interesting
is that implies in that moment which is
clearly insightful in hindsight and you
really embrace it hopefully reaping some
benefits of that today it does imply
that you routed a good number of people
probably that were not previously
familiar with working with llms or these
sort of statistical systems and
specifically a good number of deps to
work on it is that correct and I guess
how did that how easy or hard was it to
get a bunch of people citize the sort of
new way of working so the timeline goes
something like Chach Launches on a
Thursday it's Thursday evening in Dublin
Ireland where we're playing with it I'm
slacking with our VP fergo of he's our
VP of AI we really he's very convinced
and he convinces me with examples that
like this is a thing this is a big thing
I speak with own on Friday and spoke
with own through the weekend 's our CEO
in intercom and ultimately this is a
time in a company where you need an
extremely decisive and fast moving CEO
who's not in any way say Paralyzed by
risk or fear and almost just let's go I
think we should really go for it so uh
by Monday we we got to work prioritizing
the first wave of the features which
actually wasn't fan it was stuff we
built inside the inbox to augment the
support workflow so things like
automatic summarization or things like
reframing rewriting all the sort of
stuff that support reptils all the time
we were just trying to like basically
augment their workflow by removing all
the undifferentiated heavy lifting we
released those features in about seven
weeks or so and we probably put outside
of the AI group who you know obviously
would always be working in this area we
probably pushed maybe like 20 more
people at that time uh most of our inbox
team some and some of the surrounding
teams got to work on it but by January
we started to get word that GPT 4 was
coming and that was the big unlock and
that was where we're like oh GPT 4 had
we had the ability to prompt that in
such a way that it wouldn't hallucinate
at the same rate that 3.5 was and that's
when we realized if this thing if we can
control the hallucinogenic properties of
this and dial them down we can really
build the end to end answer the damn
question but so we we launched before
Sor before you go into that so before CH
GPT 4 or sorry before GPT 4 the tools
they were not internal they were
customer facing tools but they were more
I guess kind of fair to call them AI
assisted they're sort of
I'm going to you a of that gr work it's
to your customers just not to confuse
it's not to your support people it's to
the support people that are the the
terms get trickier obviously we have a
support team that's not who I'm talking
about but our customers are people who
support their customers so when we say
like we say agent facing as the tools we
built like I in Customer Support agents
got access to these tools so if they're
dealing with a ticket or a conversation
they could click a button that would
generate a summary of it their customer
our customers didn't see that was what
fin unlocked Finn was like the bot that
could actually talk to our customers on
our customers behalf yeah understood
cool okay so so you've got it so you
jump on the bandwagon you don't go right
away to the biggest audience that would
see this you would go to meet you went
to the medium audience that would see
this which is your but it's the people
paying you so I mean you care to kind of
make them happy and to like you and you
give them attend it helpful featur it's
also for what it's like this is probably
something at this but it was like the
lower risk thing to build as well
because if it generates a bad
summarization that's not a fatal outcome
right however giving an awful answer to
somebody automatically and then nobody
knowing it happened is actually a far
more dangerous so that's why we figured
it was an easier dipy toe type feature
yeah no perfect it sounds Super Wise and
we'll dig a bit more into like attended
and autonomous and all that a bit later
okay cool but so you have gp4 then you
see that Finn you see the opportunity of
Finn and then you do allocate more
people to come work yeah I think at that
point it grew to maybe a 100 people or
so across because like teams from our
messenger team various different backend
teams Finn Works off like articles so
our knowledge-based team who owns our
like a docs product they got involved as
well so it became like a companywide
initiative in loads of ways and then all
of our marketing had to shift and uh
focus on this specific product so very
quickly it became a huge chunk if not
the majority of the R&D or was working
on either direct this product directly
or the ancillary product that feed this
product yeah we have the pleasure
dubious pleasure of sort of building llm
based products at tessel I've had some
of that at sneak it's different they're
annoying they are hard to evaluate
whether you're doing your job correctly
or not sometimes costs are different
cicd is different some of the tools are
quite immature and we're talking
probably a year before that experience
that I'm referring to here how hard was
it for a developer who previously didn't
work in that surrounding to adapt it how
did you help the the dev team not just
hey I reprioritize this feature or am I
overblowing the the
change I know the the change is Big U
it's actually been a subject of a lot of
internal debate um I'll give the
umbrella answer and then we can get to
specifics in a little bit but like
generally speaking everything about how
we build software products change is
when you bring in generative AI
probability based systems or whatever
you want to call call it does classic
product development is some sort of like
Double Diamond it's like research make
decisions build like ship and then see
if it works whatever you have like extra
diamonds all over the place when it's
like AI because it's you don't start
with here to user problem let's solve it
you you tend to start with like what's
technically possible to begin with and
then you say hey does this new technical
capability let's say hey we can read
PDFs in a second okay does that map onto
any problems that we have to solve for
our users and you find one of those and
then so then you've worked out this
thing can be built and it seems like it
solves this
problem even then everyone's DNA and
software is so build it and ship it and
move on to the next feature what's the
big deal and I think the problem is once
these things go live you still don't
know if it works on them so you have to
do so much you know whereas in typical
boring bread and butter B2B sass someone
oh I wonder can we merge expenses okay
so you get two receipts you have to
combine them oh okay if you ship that
feature and people use it you're like
great you're not sitting here going oh I
wonder if it works you're assuming that
like the mathematics worked or whatever
yeah where in all these systems like
once it goes live it goes through a
whole other like almost like product
Evolution which is it actually working
the way we thought it did and obviously
we do our best to not just test these
systems on what we call Happy paths a
happy path is like how do I reset my
password an unhappy path is hey my
account is stored in my husband's name
and it's my credit card and I need to
move it to his credit card but also we
need to change address at the same time
right that's where like these systems
struggle massively they're all brilliant
at like how do I reset my password in
the same way if me and Einstein sit down
and take a maths test and it's just
basic arithmetic I look as a as smart as
Einstein so you have to have this higher
pass filter to get you but nothing like
reality bats last in AI it's the last
person to step up and and reality tells
you like hey Finn works great in all
these circumstances but here's a pocket
that it doesn't work in here's an area
that that can't reach or whatever so I
think the first thing I'd say to the
question of enabling devs and paring
devs to work in this llm first world is
like getting out of your head the idea
that things just simply do or don't work
because it's all a spectrum now getting
out of your head the that your core job
is to just clarify or remove ambiguity
ambiguity is all over the place it's and
your job is it's such a there's like an
art and science to like threading all
the needles to finding the useful
Solutions and that's before we've
actually sat down in front of a text
Setter and started buying out code
that's is in working out what problem we
could solve why we think it's Sol like
most of your prototypes in this era are
like written by just prompting my llm
and seeing what it does with certain
prompts and seeing what how it does in
response to certain asks and based if
you can get to a consistent reliable set
of behaviors then you can start to think
about how would we producti this what
are the API calls and then what's the UI
look like and then how would we describe
it and all that but you have so much
like pre work to do all that said there
is obviously around any given uh like
product if we just I'll take F because
it's the one I know best there is still
a lot of like bread and butter B2B SAU
[ __ ] you have to build someone has to
import docks and somebody has to have
permissions and it has to be charged for
it sort of Sur pricing feature like it's
not all it's not like you're you're an
llm engineer or book but it's just it's
the the secondary features that are kind
of like fall into the classic like our
reporting engine still draws graphs that
that's not
new like like engine if you build any
sort of proper product at the end of the
day the engine is 10 20% of the surface
of the product exactly that and I think
the that's there's a whole thin wrapper
thick wrapper debate that happens a lot
in the industry and I think like Finn is
very much like a thick wrapper there's a
lot around Finn that needs to be there
to make it work really well such that
the actual the pieces are like the
little like the the resolution engine
that sits inside of it that is a part of
the puzzle it's a really important high
impact part but it alone isn't
sufficient it still needs to 16 other
things to Vector search the content
import and all that sort of stuff so it
sounds like sounds like a massive change
sounds like the a lot of the changes in
the is in the sum the total of the
product there's a good chunk of people
that are still working on things that
don't require them to change their ways
of working but still a good portion that
did maybe yeah in the in the total so I
guess are there some key takeaways like
I'm sure you've tried things and some
worked you had a little bit of a head
start because you did have some AI
capabilities you
had but we had an AI product live since
I think 2017 2018 so like we we
definitely had prior experience here and
that was one of the reasons we could
move fast because we were able to reuse
a lot of our existing features for
example like the vector search engine
we' already built one for a previous
product Etc so we were that's one of the
reasons why we were like out of the
gates so fast if I was to really say
like the the biggest lessons I've
observed like to be care what I'm
skipping over here is I'm sure there are
libraries and apis and all sorts of
stuff need to read and get good at Etc
but I think um to actually be a a
performant engineer in this era requires
some amount of ability to interrogate
data or perform data science to measure
outcomes like to give you a very simple
example when we make a change we've run
probably like 50 different AB tests on
Finn's performance and it's very
tempting everyone comes in who might Jo
join the group and say something like oh
I have a cool feature I
how about we make it so that blah like
how about we make it so it'll always ask
this question at the end of the thing
and what you don't realize is like all
of these things are different iterations
of a resolution engine whose job is
ultimately to give a question anwers and
if you break that it doesn't matter how
cool your little addition was now the
thing is that's not a binary yes no
condition it's like today Fin's
performance is about 50% of so 50% of
inbound support volume will be resolved
by fit if somebody rolls at a cool
feature Fe that brings that 50 down to
40 that's a problem yeah if they do that
and don't even know to check or to
realize or to look at its performance
over a trailing 30 days whatever that's
an even bigger problem so there's a very
much you need to work out you have to
understand trick to working with these
systems is to like bottle up a
probabilistic outcome and productize it
and you have to work out who is allowed
play with the probabilities of that and
understand that it's not like two
different worlds it's very easy for
somebody in our messenger team to damage
the performance of Finn even though they
don't write to that code base but if
they frame it wrong and they introduce
Finn in the wrong way it'll change what
people right and if it changes what
people right then it'll change how Finn
performs so it's really like the the
extra skill required here is the ability
to assess does this thing do the job
it's supposed to do at a really high
performance level and you have to some
way to measure that some way to test it
have bake offs of different against each
other some way to have an acceptance
framework for when all right that's been
live for 30 days no one's complained it
looks like we got a 4% increase in in
resolutions ship it it's like that none
of those skills really existed before in
I'd say in most companies but definitely
not in intercome yeah no it sounds
fascinating I guess the good news is
there's some analogy between what you're
describing and the state-ofthe-art in
terms of continuous deployment right if
you're working with fut Flags if you're
in Facebook and you're shipping I forget
the name of their sort of future system
there some gradual number of people then
there's some similarity of it but this
is much more n Mass much more
predictable pretty much does it kill
almost substantially the value of a sort
of cicd assessment for anything that
isn't the more bread and butter sasp how
much having run with this now for a bit
how trustworthy or how revealing are the
results of the synthetic tests or the
cicd type the predeployment tests that
you have yeah I mean we have two tests
we have one test we perform internally
which is expensive to R which is like
our torture test so let's just say
torture test it's it's all the psychotic
scenarios that F will get put into in
the real world but we where we want to
make sure it doesn't like barf so we
don't do this unless we have good reason
but let's just say like GPT 4 Z drops or
something like that or 40 the tempting
thing to do and you'll see a lot of our
competitors do this is just holy [ __ ]
new model plug it in we're good and and
I think what that says to me is it
speaks to the maturity of their roll out
like we also know the same API end
points to Ping if you want 40 it's like
it's not we weren't sitting going wonder
how do you do this it says our approach
to such a scenario is okay let's first
of all run distri the torture test and
our torture test is there to
deliberately give us hard situations
where we have a very clear outcome so
for example let's say Tesla is using fin
would you want tessels bought to
recommend competitors over tesle would
you want it to would you want it to
answer a tier three question if it did
know the answer how would you want it to
behave would you want it to make up an
answer a long variety like genuinely
hundreds of scenarios where most people
agree on what the right outcome is uh
but like GPT 40 might not agree with
that so this is where like you have to
control and contain the behavior so once
it clears the torture test and we look
at its performance then we'll move to
look let's put this live let's see how
it works in actual reality which often
times is just in a gradual fashion like
you wouldn't turn it on for everybody
you would graduate you would yes
absolutely and I think there is a lot of
parallels to cicd except for this year
it's almost say if you're Facebook
rolling at cicd and you know let's move
the Poke button to the left from the
left to the right or something like that
okay that probably will change human
behavior and it's probably in a hard to
guess way we have that problem and then
on top of that we have the the fact of
we don't even know what poke does most
of the time but
0% show up on the right or on the left
on the right
yeah everyone I'll get it's like when
you multiply in probabilities they tend
to grow yeah super interesting so this
is fascinating so you move to to really
glow all in on AI you're highlighting
that there's still a lot of like core
SAS that has to be built you know for
The Full Experience on it but you have
to change your total approach to product
to in some respects really embrace the
sort of continuous deployment type Tye
model but really probably more
supercharged and that requires
developers to have a lot more ability to
interrogate data that's work in that
fashion how has that changed like when
you look at the team are there either
did you have to recalibrate and actually
move some people out of that team or
hire for some skills and and maybe a bit
more gently for new people that you hire
is there a difference in the skill set
You're Now searching for yeah yeah we
distinguish right now between uh
engineers in our AI group on engineers
in what we call a core product it's a
different like generally speaking we're
like Ruby on rail shop we we tend to
hire like Engineers that are full stock
or close to full stock and we still need
a lot of them like as I said the
reporting engine for fin has like date
Pickers and graphs and charts and
Sliders and all the [ __ ] you'd expect
and none of that is is like head
scratchy type stuff it's an average CS
degree produces people who can do all
that the the extra skills we look for
with IND the group are is everything
around data science it's everything
around basically like data driven
decisions and it's got there's a hard
requirement on the ability to
interrogate performance that's what we
actually need we tend to hire an indoc
group so a lot of our products begin
life inside the AI group until we are
sure that we've got the core engine
performing then we when we when it comes
to productizing it and building out all
of the as you said the sort of the SAS
standard wrapping type stuff that's
necessary to utilize the engine that's
when we hand it over to people and for
those folks we're not sitting here going
oh I wonder what the DAT picker is going
to do today we know how to do all that
sort of stuff so we right now I think
this will change over time but right now
we just basically say there's pockets of
our sort of overall engineering or where
we deal with significant uncertainty
that is that needs containment and there
are people who usually write against the
llms and that take scenarios do testing
and all that sort of stuff and then just
the the rest of of the work which is
like productizing what what has been
coming out of the AI group so we haven't
changed our kind of core definition of
an engineer but when we're hiring
Engineers to join the AI group we have
extra requirements if you're a brilliant
research scientist who's wonderful data
and it's really good at say programming
but has never really built a web app
before his historically we might not
have had much of a job for you now we
might have in our infra team or
something like that but now we're like
it doesn't actually bother us you don't
need to be like brilliant likeing react
or Amber or whatever to to perform in
the AI group what you do need to some
skills along those lines actually she
product eyes which is why you'd probably
join R&D if you had that skill set yeah
interesting but it also sounds like the
AI engineering is not all phds in
machine learning it is software
Engineers with data bias or somewhere
between yeah learning Engineers with
software bias and vice versa yeah there
is a higher percentage of machine of
phds in the AI group for sure I think a
lot of that comes from fgo's desire to
have people who are very capable of
running their own data analysis on their
own work and typically those skills tend
to get most perhaps battle hardened in
research so I'm guessing I'm confident
there's more phds or MSS or whatever in
Doc group I'd say the reason is what I
said which is just the ability to
perform your own analysis at a pretty
deep level what without needing much
oversight which you might not get in in
a regular computer science degree but
but we've had like multiple successful
Engineers leave a regular stuff and go
and join the AI group and perform really
well yeah so it's different skills I'm
curious a little bit whether this would
lead into kind of research entities or
will the industry of developing on top
of this ai go maybe the way of design
and others in which you'll find yourself
wanting to have trials or maybe now it's
quads of teams or domains
Associated AI accompan it's a great
question so right now it's it's an
opinionated thing we're doing to say the
AI group exists here and people who
build products that wrap the AI group
stuff to you commercialize it exists
elsewhere there are benefit costs and
benefits in a sense right you can guess
all of the challenges of having people
hinge on like right now in a classic
intercom engineering team there like an
engineering manager a designer a product
manager and maybe five Engineers what
they don't yet specifically have on
every team is like the AI person because
the actual products like aren't built
like distri in a distributed way
products are built in a centralized way
in the AI group and as I said that
engine then gets taken out and the
engine is what gets all the product
built around it and then that's what we
launch yeah yeah interesting we'll see
how that evolves and how that counters
the other best practice that evolves
around less full stack teams right that
can yeah yeah like it's it's very clear
the trade-offs we make in both
directions to be clear yeah so maybe
let's ship gears a little bit and talk
talk about the learnings on the product
side so you as as we mentioned you had a
chat-based product you also had the AI
maybe Head Starts a little bit in the
organization but still you had a chat
based product so the interface or at
least it's easy for me from the outside
it's easy to understand how chat GPT
will interact with Finn or will augment
or even create Finn to doing it how
significant do you think it is to have
already an existing chat interface or
Lang interface uh do do you think the
same urgency of the sort of Code Red
that you pulled is appropriate in other
domains or or is it really like an order
of magnitude more urgent for people that
are already
talking like are already chat based do
you mean like specifically in customer
service or do you mean just broadly in
the industry I think in the industry in
Industries as a whole if you just talk
about products or how significant was it
that your product was already chart
based I yeah it's it's a good question I
haven't actually thought about just too
much I'll tell it's it made it very damn
obvious what we have to do next because
obviously overnight people got used to
just typing into chat GPT and chat GT
GPT seems so smart that like anywhere
else you type it's not chat GPT now it
seems dumb right or CLA or any of those
so I think like for a lot of our
competitors who had say maybe who worked
in customer support but had a ticket
first mindset or an email support first
mindset I think it probably was very
alarming to them because they were like
oh [ __ ] intercom had this right all
along in that if chat was gonna happen
and AI if AI was gonna happen then chat
was gonna be the obvious conduit so you
s we saw a lot of people scrambling to
copy our Messenger as best as they could
and then also go and try and copy our
fin as best as they could too right so I
think with in support it was obvious but
if I just take a study broader thing I
think chat UI is a fascinating area and
I think the next year we'll we'll see
and voice is part of this as well but
let me just say a few different things
one is like
what cha driven UI offers us is a way to
use products where you know the outcome
you want and you know how to explain
what it is that you want but up until
now the UI has been the barrier that you
didn't know how to use so to give you a
simple example maybe you do or don't
know how to use Photoshop right maybe
you know a little bit a few layers and
you know a couple of effect you don't
really get it so if I gave you a photo
and say can you remove the foreground
from the background or can you make
Dez's t-shirt green instead of white or
whatever you know what it is you want
you have probably have an idea of your
end outcome but you probably just don't
know how to do it and that's an
interesting barrier that like UI design
and the whole usability era of 20056 78
n was about this it was about like how
can we make all of these Arcane
Technologies easier to use it turns out
the easiest UI to use will often be one
where you just need to explain what it
is you want to do so you probably have
somewhere in the depth of Tesla an Excel
spreadsheet that tracks your Revenue
growth or will you will at some point
and uh you might well be like how can I
forecast this there for three years and
assume to growth degrades andur up ticks
and retention and N or and the answer is
lots of formula that you don't know off
for H and yet you're in a world where
you actually do know the thing you want
to do so what chat and then what soon
voice will be just like I think when
Apple launches Apple intelligence for
real and assuming it doesn't suck what I
think you'll see is everyone just gets
used to saying things almost speaking to
the computer more like it's an actual
servant who actually understands them
and the so the net effect is people will
assume that they can use software
because they just need to say what it is
that they want so I think products that
haven't here to before adopted a chat
driven UI might want to think about it
because it might just or like a Voice
driven UI because whilst there are still
some obvious power tools where like
pointing and clicking and dragging and
I'm thinking about an example let's say
you're editing a movie and you want to
overlap time zone sorry timelines and
all sort there are clear power tools for
that well those power tools are going to
be much more like the back of the
toolbox and not like the hammer or
screwdriver I think you you might end up
thinking about like voice UI and chat UI
as the hammer and screwdriver is in
everyone has one and then if you need to
you've got the big dirty [ __ ] tool
box you keep in the garage for occasions
when you need it and and I think you'll
be surprised how many things you can get
done just by saying the thing you want
to do even these are like those Facebook
uh Ray bands the metag glasses sorry
like even that is like quite impressive
for what I can get you done and that's
just Meta Meta like whatever it's called
Lama like I think everyone's interaction
mode with software is going to change
and they're just going to get used to
not learning how to use Microsoft Word
or figma or whatever and in a load of
cases unless it's a specialist tool just
saying the thing you want done and
getting it done and and that that just
changes the nature of software and it
massively democratizes it like in two
years time everyone might be brilliant
that Excel that might just be the case
anyway so that that's how I think about
that I think like some people started
like we we were at chat UI all along for
loads of different reasons and so is
like say SL for you it supercharges like
it just it makes a product 10 times
better but it doesn't require a change
in how users interact with it it just
succeeds that much more often I think
that's totally correct even if any of
your our listeners have driven a modern
fancy car where you can press a button
and say please turn on the air
conditioning and defrost a windscreen or
something like that that's actually when
it works and again that's a massive as
risk for a lot of these things but when
it works it's way better than these
weird buttons on your dash you're kind
of stabbing hoping but if you can just
say the thing you want and get it that
is that's remarkable yeah that's a very
that's a a very useful and and I agree
with like good analogy of areas in which
a chat-based interface will help I think
what's interesting and so maybe
connecting it a little bit to to code I
guess two questions first just on
interface in AI Dev tools two of the
most prominent use cases that are
already getting adoptions are code
completion in the IDE Pilots of the
world and next to them pull request
related items or review uh a change on
it and I guess when I think about those
navely I feel like the completion piece
isn't based by default its completion it
it is text based a different one while
the PLL request review is chat based
it's asynchronous so it's interesting
you compared it to a ticket based
approach maybe it's it'll be good to
maybe hear that distinction I guess I I
wonder that based on your experience
generally like what you've seen the
Euros or the experience with Finn do you
feel the llms are more aligned to one of
those approaches or or to something else
like with the advantage of the chat
based sort of approach that exists in
poor
requests give it an edge of not of of
adoption at least forget about
capability even but just like adoption
because people are already used to
interacting with this through
chats yeah there's a bit there I think
that when I think about what completion
actually is which is let's just say you
like you you stub out a method and you
put in a kind of pseudo code comment
saying here's what's going to happen and
then you just hit the magic go button
and like and the thing you wanted to do
it is it's another variation of the
describing how I want something
describing the outcome I want in a way
and and getting it and saving me like
the pain of the interface in between
which sometimes is point and click and
sometimes it's just typing out a for
Loop or whatever right um I think there
is like a similarity put it this way I
don't know if that binary exists between
let's just say the completion and say
like a state based thing like review
this pull request whatever uh they're
not miles apart from each other I think
chat UI basically offers people a way to
say write the thing you're trying to do
and hit return and it'll get done and I
think completion is like a different
instantiation of the same principle
which is like describe roughly Loosely
what it is you're trying to get done hit
the magic button and see if it gets done
if you don't like it provide more
context and and then like the risk with
say going like in the case of most of
the completions St I've seen that's just
GitHub copot one I'm most familiar with
but I've looked at cursor and a few of
the other ones what I find like it's
quite a risky move because if it doesn't
work it's [ __ ] we've dealt with this
quite a bit and we can talk about that
when we talk about our own assist of
product co-pilot where to some degree
the measure of how confident you are has
to drive your UI decision because if
you're like so maybe just to get into it
to exemplify that point if you're sure
that nine nine and a half times out of
10 you're going to be right then you can
design it such that it naturally assumes
it's correct and embeds it in that way
so it just goes so rather than popping
you a dialogue saying I think you're
trying to ride a loop does this look
like and you have to say yes and all
that you just in inject it directly
because you're you have the confidence
that makes sense to give you an example
of a change we made we were building a
at a um effectively completion uh for
customer support teams so uh new new
conversation comes into the inbox uh you
read the conversation and you start
typing and what we were hoping we could
do would be like tab auto complete and
hit send and wouldn't that be a
wonderful experience and in practice
it's not like when you test this on the
happy path it's very easy to solve it
works well yeah yeah when you test this
on the torture test or anything like
real world usage it doesn't work at the
same rate at all it blur Blends in [ __ ]
like pii it confuses scenarios it
confuses types of users it says too much
it says too little because of all that
the right place the right UI design to
wrap around this was not injected into
the text area so that somebody can press
return and instead what we actually
built was a right hand sidebar called C
where you can diagnose the issue select
the pieces search knowledge bases look
for related conversations but you
basically have a chat on the right hand
side with like the co-pilot who's
effectively an expert trained on every
conversation that's ever happened in
your business right and like the reason
we built all that other software was
because we couldn't do the thing we
wanted the thing we wanted was not going
to be feasible which would be in line
the and so so I love that you're saying
two things one is complete completion
and whatever chat based interactions are
not that distinct in both cases you're
describing I love the comment example
because comment is very much a chapter
you're talking to your future self in a
second here I'm gonna write this thing
or in my sort of future person who comes
in to to read this code this is what the
next bits C so that that aligns with
your previous example of why do I need
to know which icon to press on the the
car dashboard can you just tell me to
turn on the air conditioning so I like
that but then to an extent even as you
type it in all of that can be seen which
I guess it is as a chat you're talking
to it whether or not you're doing it in
line or not whether it's chat offline is
really is just a matter of confidence if
you have doing it I I do think like I I
relate to that I feel like there's a
little bit of push backing that the chat
thing is is is often wrong and I think
the inline option gives you every time I
press a key you have an opportunity to
give me something different right if the
if the chat on the side told me
something and then if I didn't press the
copy button out of that 5 seconds later
it would give me something else and 5
seconds later that would turn off that
pain pretty quickly but in the in the
code that it runs yeah that's there's an
interesting point there which is like
how much context are you willing to feed
the more context you feed the more cost
you paid to use this feature but also
the greater the chance of certainty a
CTIC intercom situation would be like
some people write into support under
first question is high are you there
right right that's not going to do
anything useful for you with that right
be answer is yes I am really here my
name is really Dez I am here to support
you and they say I have a problem we're
still getting nowhere right you know and
I say what's the down problem they say
the screen doesn't work and I'm like you
have to really press and all that stuff
to some degree you have to do sometimes
you have to do a lot of work to feed it
enough states such that it'll guess
correctly what it what it should do next
and a version of that might be like if
you're playing with say claw and it's
like its ability to say generate
complete Ops whatever you can say build
me a game or you can say build me a game
called Pon or you can say build me a
game called po poon whereas the yellow
character in AE is with ghosts and he
runs around and he eats pills and the
more State you give it the more cost
you're paying but also the more
Precision you get in output it's almost
I always used to say to people going
back to the jobs to be done school I
thought that we used to talk about a lot
back in the day in intercom I would
often say if someone says I am hungry
you don't know what to get if someone
says I'm running through an airport
starving and I need something to eat
that's going to fill me up while I'm on
to go and I only have one hand free then
you're like here's a slice of pizza it's
like the problem describes the solution
the more detail on the problem more
detail on the solution and I think
there's a similarity there for prompt as
well and what you're describing is if
you're a pretty good coder which I'm
guessing you are and you're like
knocking out like a pretty descriptive
code and you're like halfway through a
method that you've probably thrown a few
comments into along the way yeah it's
going to be able to toab auto complete
the rest of the entire file for you if
you start off with please build me
Pacman or whatever it might be like do
you want a 3D engine do you want two
it's going to myfire a lot more so I
just think prompting or like giving
context to the engine is a kind of an a
I based thing and the benefit of these
like really specific llms is that they
make a few assumptions on your behalf
which reduces the investment and
increases the return yeah yeah no I
think that all makes sense I think the
so the other lens of this equation to to
your analoges on the UI that I really
liked is your ability to specify it so
you give example of I want to turn that
shirt red so the the instruction is
simple your desire is simple but the
application of it is complic at
sometimes the instruction is not that
trivial right like when you think we
talk about AI native software
development we talk about it being spech
Centric versus code Centric and one of
the challenges we're playing with in
learning is how do you specify how do
you know to say that Pac-Man is 2D
versus 3D how do you know which
questions to ask and then sometimes
proactively which information to
volunteer and I think like maybe
importantly how do you draw the line
because if you don't say something
then the llm will provide will will make
assumptions right assuming you hav't
blocked it from doing that and you can
give it context about yourself about
coding in the world about the the
application how how do you control the
degree of Freedom that you you want to
give it let me like if you can cast your
mind back to when you're learning how to
code and at some point somebody
introduced you to the concept of pseudo
code and specifically maybe it wasn't
you maybe you were that damn good but
somebody in your class was probably much
better at pseudo code than they wereare
at code which always led to the
discussion of why can't you just compile
pseudo code because that would be a lot
damn easier right and the answer as we
all learn over time because I load was I
certainly did I'm sure you did as well
we tried to write a pseudo code compiler
H and the answer always comes out the
following which is if you want
specificity and output you need
specificity and input right and the
modern day version of this is why does
all the AI writing sound the same right
the answer is because you the Brilliance
of these things is that you give it such
a small prompt and it can be so
evocative and prescriptive how how does
it know what to use the word brilliant
or gorgeous how does it know how does it
know any of these things because it's
making assumptions and it's costing you
like it's robbing you of that ability
for exp sorry your desire to short
prompt is robbing you of the ability to
add in detail and description which
means you're not going to control the
output either so that's ultimately the
the Paradox we're playing with here is
we want to have like somehow the
smallest possible set of inputs but we
also want extreme diversity in the set
of outputs and the reality is much like
the reason you can't we can't actually
compile pseudo code or like you can but
you it's not the same strength as an
actual full programming language is
because the desire for detail is at odds
with the desire for minimal prompting so
did so to your question it's it's the
amount of description you are willing to
provide a scenario will reward you on
the far side with the detail and the
llms can say let's always let's say we
build an llm for a keyboard powered 2D
game now I can probably just say build
Pacman or build arcanoid or something
like that right we've baked in so much
stuff already or it doesn't even need to
be at the LM level it could be at a
silent prompt behind the scenes level or
something like that but but in doing so
we've cost yourself we've shrank our
world massively so this is this is I
think going to be one of the big tests
we see as llms evolve over the next
couple years is do these verticalized
llms truly outperform because in some
sense they're power comes from their
specificity but that also means that
they've had to delete whole Chun world
to achieve that you know what I mean
yeah I do and and I think it's super
interesting I think one angle on that is
that sometimes you want to be creative
but oftentimes you want to work within
an ecosystem or within a context so like
within an organization you don't want to
every time explain it if you are a
builder of 3D games for the whatever
Nintendo switch and that's what we
you're doing you don't need to say that
every time to the talk about an
application in your world I often wonder
like an llm trained only on the entire
WordPress ecosystem would it be better
or worse done an LL train all all code
ever when it comes to writing WordPress
plugins and it's hard I don't know the
answer to that question I want to say
the whole world will will be better but
actually from a raw productivity get it
right every time blah blah blah point of
view like when you shrink the world
maybe and like our version of this like
we look at building say llms training
them on C sport conversations blah blah
blah all that sort of stuff but it's not
obvious to me do we want a support rep
of the future to have only ever heard
support conversations or should they
have read Shakespeare it's it's not
obvious and I don't think we actually
know the answer in in society at uh how
much generalizable knowledge is useful
in verticalized instances basically yeah
and and I think I actually really want
to drill into that sort of future AI
native support I'm going keep that to
the end but maybe one tactical question
on is like how significant is it in
terms of success today when you give
Finn the existing knowledge base I'm
sure you have some customers that have
populated with a lot of information
versus some that populated so I guess
like how significant is it for it to get
the right answer and are you seeing any
already some gaps of Hey look it's it's
becoming robotic it's only if I gave it
so much information it really stays
within the lines and that's nice but it
means it it can deal actually worse than
others with with problems that are just
on the edge yeah so direct right content
is is a huge part of the what makes fin
work having access to up to- date for
honestly the most common experience an
unhappy Finn customer has is they give
us their knowledge base and Finn starts
reading their knowledge base and
replying as if the knowledge base was
true and that triggers a realization of
our knowledge base is year a day our
support team knew this but they never
time to update it and so like that is a
thing like the right information like
Finn deifies the content that you give
it over its General intellect so it will
prioritize that and then like the
interesting thing that we often observe
is we do a lot of work to control
hallucinations and we do that because
the nature of fin is if you like have
100 100,000 conversations a month in the
future with tessla and let's say if fin
has like a0 2% hallucination rate which
it doesn't but if it did it means like
whatever 200 people are getting the
wrong answer and you don't even know and
they might even follow the instructions
in the answer and they don't even know
either so all of this can go wrong
however the work we do to control
hallucinations can often suppress our
resolution engine because B basally Finn
let's say Finn is really good for up to
50% if you want if you're willing to
hallucinate you can get a lot higher
than that but but you're just stepping
into the unnown so your actual
resolutions will go but so will your bad
answers where so there's a tension there
of like how um like how much risk do you
want to bake in if you like yeah and do
you have you considered engaging the
customer with that have you considered
saying the customer hey I don't know
that answer I can try and get more
creative but then I might get it wrong
do you want that do
Finn currently would do is it'll give
you a sense of its own confidence so if
you say is the store open on Monday at
10 a.m. it will say yes if you say is
the store open on Christmas Day at 3M it
will say I don't know here's the
information I've read which suggests
that the answer might be blah but you
should verify yourself H and and I think
that's in line with how we would want a
human to behave which is a lot of what
we're trying to do is like mimic a kind
of best-in-class support rep and because
like in the future what we want Finn to
do is if doesn't know Finn should jump
into slack and post and say hey guys
question for you that I don't have the
answer to and then the people who reply
to Finn in slack Finn will take that say
it back to the user and then possibly go
and update the knowledge base so that it
has the information for the future
that's the full endend workflow you
you'd like of a support like proper yeah
no I think that's very valuable I'm
curious so thinking about that context
it's interesting to apply it to the
world of code generation there's a
there's a set of really formidable uh
products and companies right now looking
to
improve code completion AI code
generation as a whole by indexing an
Enterprise's existing code base I don't
know I'm kind of asking for a prediction
do you think I can see how they would
realize most of their codebase is crap
and they do almost like the knowledge
base being out of days no no I don't
want to replicate this sort of debt read
code based on it don't replicate these
bad practices of the past I can also see
constraint but also at the same time
it's pretty easy to understand how hey
you would learn organizational behaviors
and it would seem a bit more like a
developer in this company I don't know
if you were giving advice you to to
anybody building that type of of code
completion that is infused with existing
organizational codebase information what
would you say yeah there's a slight
difference I'll answer it directly in a
sec but there's a slight difference the
knowledge based thing is real and it's
definitely like if you give I'm sure
copy code will get you more copy code
and in in our world the wrong docs will
get you the wrong answers um the there
are some differences in that like I
think people more naturally how would
you say maintain their code base perhaps
than they do their knowledge base which
can't actually sit on a shelf somewhere
it's also the case though that like most
companies like they'll give a good talk
about style guide and tone of voice but
actually if you go and read 10 different
docs by 10 different support people
they're written in 10 different styles
and it's totally fine whereas I think
that companies try to through linting
inorder S of try to enforce a kind of
standard uh a bit more of a standard
when I think what would it look like to
um let's just say train up or take as
input a company's entire c-base like I I
don't know but what I'd say is generally
speaking you get more of what you give
it so the challenges you'd have is let's
say your your early code was [ __ ] and
and over time you got really good if
it's a 8020 [ __ ] code versus good you're
going to advance or propagate that is
one worry I'd have secondly I I worry
how do you perform like cultural
Transformations because if the if you're
saying hey guys we need to really like
care about from this point onward like
you could possibly try and prompt an LM
like let's care about that but in
general it's if it's learned entirely
off what it's seen so far it's just
going to keep doing what it's seen so
far and then like there are like I I
guess there's other stuff where going
back to our earlier point if you're
asking it to do something that it hasn't
seen at all before that has no predicate
in the existing cbase it'll probably end
up like riffing or doing its best but
they'll probably be like some it'll
probably take you new directions that
you might not have gone which is which
is sometimes good and sometimes very bad
yeah it's a challenge like in general
interesting yeah to think about how
would how to address that in product
over time to allow the edges of
creativity to shine at the same time
maintain predictability which I guess is
also true in humans right yeah it's so
much of what we see you look at say
figma AI right like the ability to draw
interfaces like there's two different
ways people respond to that some people
are like oh my God I can't believe
you're going to take away all my like
pointy clicky pixel playing
and other people are like Hallelujah you
mean I don't have to drag boxes around
for like 25 minutes just to get to the
point where I designed something new in
the world that's often like what the
argument will make is like we will
remove all the undifferentiated heavy
lifting if you might remember dhh is
rail demo of look at what I'm not doing
the reason people were excited by that I
think it was like a blog or something he
sted out 10 seconds the reason people
were excited because all the
undifferentiated boring [ __ ] and
programming was taken away or made very
elant with bits of Ruby or whatever so
that you could actually do something new
in the world and I think you could argue
that did the proper adoption of AI
native code generation would mean that
like people only write semantically deep
really meaningful lines of code that
really matter to the true nature of the
product that they're building which
paradoxically means that code completion
will become less useful right the reason
for that is because if AI is generating
like 90% of the undifferentiated [ __ ]
the piece it can't generate has no
precedent so that's and I would say the
same thing like an interesting thing
that happens when people adopt fin is
the average handling time of their and
the number of tickets dealt with per day
of their support team goes up not down
why is that because all the easy shit's
gone and what that means is so what your
humans are left with is the stuff that
really requires human intellect and I
think you'll see this code generation as
well we'll generate all the easy stuff
and then what's left is the stuff that's
not easy to generate go you better you
better start writing it you know yeah
and that story kind of repeats in AI a
fair bit which is sometimes people need
the simple tasks because they want that
as a as a break absolutely yeah so we
talked a lot about sort of product
learnings and about building a product
that's AI C actually talked about
adapting the dev practices as well do
you feel the same urgency around
becoming AI powered like how do you
think about your own Dev team and your
own team Beyond Dev as well using AI
powered tools do you feel the same
urgency about it have you done anything
what's your view there I think all of
our Engineers or the vast majority of
them have and Ed things like co-pilot so
I I believe and I'm sure like one
challenge for us is that just that we're
a little bit at scale like we're like a
thousand people we have substantial
infrastructure Etc so like a lot of the
cool advancements whether it's like AI
power let's just say endtoend testing
like an AI version of selenium and all
that sort of stuff I think all of those
are coming out these days but they might
just need to mature a little bit before
we can actually properly adopt them but
I think there's definitely I don't know
if it's urgency so much as was desire to
like to get on board with being an AI an
AI first as just say R&D or product or
in general we also use there a lot of
other areas like you know AI summaries
of meetings ai ai analysis like one of
the things we look at a lot we get like
you know thousands of feature requests
we use AI to roll up all that so we use
it in all the obvious ways or at least
what I hope are obvious to most people
on our marketing side I would like us to
use more of it and certainly on sales I
think there's probably opportunities as
well as it relates to like either
qualification or prospecting or any of
that there are great tools out there
I've invested in a chunk of them things
like 11x for like basically an SD or a
box type products there are there will
be like endtoend marketing tools which
will like start companions turn on odws
you know send prospects emails all that
sort of stuff I don't think we're
adopting anything yet amazing there
there's other stuff we're looking like
things like Synthesia for like synthetic
video avatars all that sort of [ __ ] I
think that that will also be like a part
of the future what do I feel urgency
there I think I'll I probably want to
make sure that we're moving as fast as
is no I should be clear I don't control
these areas there are other people make
these decisions but I hope we're moving
as fast as it's sensible I also know
that a lot of these tools a lot of the
AI tools if we're being really honest
they don't have in my mind enough
discipline regard regarding testing and
making sure that they both deliver the
outcomes and don't deliver negative
outcomes do like quite often I'm sure
all of your listeners have had this
experience they sign up for some tool
the Talk's a big game on the marketing
website they download it they try to do
the thing whether it's a generate the
report or write the email whatever and
it birs and I think you know you have to
be cautious in your adoption of AI
especially if you're an not scale
business because the last thing we want
is a is a a shitty email going out to
like people it's interesting because
it's the same it's the same comment on
you don't know whether the product works
or not that you talked about when you're
building
productt it's the same as a consumer
right you're consuming a product
absolutely you don't know if it works
the fact that it worked in the demo the
fact that it worked five times doesn't
mean it would work a sixth and so you
have to have more it's it's 100% that
guy but it's also again having seen a
lot of these companies up close and
personal I don't I don't conviction that
a lot of them have enough discipline or
hygiene around what they will roll out
and I mean that genuinely in it's very
tempting to be like hey Claude claude's
New Frontier Model just dropped stick it
in and pick go and see what happens
right like if there's real customers on
the far side of that people are going to
get affected in in not so great ways and
that's no fault of anthropic it's just I
don't like I'm not sure that all these
like white hot new super scaling AI
startups are applying enough discipline
to the products that they're rolling out
and because of that I think it's
probably riskier in some areas we put a
lot of work into making sure people can
evaluate Finn before they go we really
want people to feel comfortable about
what's going out in front of their
customers but a lot of these products
don't give you that opportunity they
just say import your contacts and we'll
do the
rest I don't that my
life yeah hope for the best is the
exactly that's before you even opened up
authorization or any of those types of
concerns I want to talk a little bit
about attended versus autonomous and
then maybe finish off with some AI
native chat you mentioned Finn a bunch
of times as an autonomous agent and I
think of it as that as well H how do you
think about autonomy in in the world of
AI even for you for Finn what's what
does it mean that it's
autonomous and I guess maybe to play
Devil's Advocate like for if a customer
is there a customer's customer right
your customer's customer is there and
sort of says yes you've addressed my
problem or not does that qualify as
autonomous how how do you delineate
those yeah so I will get to the answer
but I'll just give a bit of structure
here if you think about any given
product is like a set of workflows so
like customer support it has the triage
workflow it has the handle a customer
query workflow it has the updated
engineer workflow and you log in and
your dashboard is usually just a navbar
that takes you to various different
workflows so the first wave of AI
products and indeed the first stuff we
shipped which was like Hey automatically
sumarized that just takes a single step
out of an existing workflow and does it
automatically and sometimes you can take
two or three steps out of workflow and
do those automatically but it's still an
attended workflow so as in somebody is
still going copying the summary and
pasting it and going over here and
clicking that and they might get a
suggestion to do this and they'll accept
the suggestion and they'll go that's
just augmenting human capacity and a lot
of the like first round of AI whether
was code AI notion AI or whatever they
were just basically saying here's a few
cool tools for your team who already
used this product that's why they all
just charge it and it's another $9 on
the seat price because we're basically
augmenting the human capacity a little
bit by taking away some of the work and
I think that's that was the Gen one of
AI products that we saw happen over the
first half of 202 still most of them
today probably yeah yeah a lot of them
are still just that the next wave is
let's take a whole workflow end to
endend and what you'll see there is
something like hey one of our most
common workflows is like optimize all of
our ads or review all of our campaigns
and cancel all the most cancel all the
least performant ones and the budget on
the expensive ones whatever or the
performance ones and if you can actually
do all of those steps in a row like the
AI is handing over to itself and it's
like basically every single step is
automated such that you basically just
tell the users don't worry this product
is always optimizing your ODS there is
no UI for that you just trust us we'll
give you a report at the end of the
month right that's like the Gen 2
products which I think you can think of
us hey a whole chunk of the job is now
gone that's great we've saved we've
saved massive amounts of human time here
right it's at least equivalent props to
salaries or whatever and then the Gen
tree which is where I think we get to
like deep proper full broadscale
autonomy is when you're replacing orgs
you're not replacing humans but you're
replacing ORS so if you take 11x as one
example 11x is like an sdor team in a
box and I really do mean team like
here's a funny example that I think this
will distinguish the the three worlds
for you in one week in mid 2023 I got
pitched three different startups this
all in one week startup one on a Tuesday
was we'll be we'll help your sales team
write emails and we'll do the
prospecting we'll do the research find
the details find a relevant for intro
point and we'll write a great email for
you yeah the second one was like you
import your CSV we'll research on all of
them and we'll send the emails too oh
wow if the second one exists the first
one doesn't right because clearly that's
the third one I got was you just
describe the customers you want like VPS
of engineering and you go and we're
going to go find them find your email
addresses write the emails send them out
set up the calendary invites and your
sdor will just get [ __ ] demos to be
scheduled or whatever right and you see
that's the way this world is going right
and I think like the you have autonomy
of the human and you autonomy of the org
and before that to Safe the dip your toe
type features is let's just make it easy
to do common repetitive tasks the humans
have to do that's roughly how I model
out the space yeah no I I I I think I
understand and you're describing it once
again like with the completion and the
context as a Continuum and you say there
isn't a magic attended versus autonomous
type lens fully it's more about the size
of the task you could say that you
summarize emails autonomously but suiz
email is not like a
sufficiently it's not what I call like
an endend work for the outcome if the
outcome is sufficiently is is is the
actual kind of goal of a workflow then
you can say it establishes it completes
this workflow autonomously yeah like the
way I think about it more is whatever
business need is presented does it get
resolved without human intervention and
if the human intervention is just to
click next and okay and next that's
still human scaled in some sense you
still need humans in the mix so that's I
haven't thought that out fully but
that's roughly what's in my mind is
basically when you properly automate the
flow no one's thinking about it or
talking about in the business it's like
it's why is the electricity working
above my head I don't know I don't care
versus something that's slightly more
complicated might be like hey every day
I'm involved in my calendar and making
sure it's got to do it like kind the
thing happen without a human input yeah
yeah I think that makes sense so I guess
maybe this leads to a good kind of close
off of AI native so if you were to
decouple from today and you were s to
imagine five plus years from now 10
years from now what is an AI native
support process like how do we
even uh consume fulfill support in that
world
I honestly I think the nature of service
changes I think you you'll see every
product every website every service
every app will have a concept of how you
get help and it'll Pro possibly it could
be audio could be video could be video
Avatar it could be human it could be any
of those things I think it'll be both
proactive and reactive it'll if I log in
and my credit card's about to expire
it'll be like yo your credit card's
about to expire click here to fix it or
whatever it won't wait for [ __ ] to go
wrong it'll make sure it things go right
I think will Humanity will have gotten
used to and expect subsecond replies to
things so the idea of thank you for your
ticket we'll get back to you in 24 to 72
hours will be like batshit it will be
simply like people expect to type
problems and get answers I think the the
specificity and detail of the answers
will dramatically improve even from
where it is today so so you'll get an
answer that is better than a human would
give you can go into further detail and
I think the the norm will therefore be
like most things go right so there just
the quality of using software will
dramatically improve because I think you
have like autonomous agents proactively
improving the support experience and
proactively improving the customer
experience in general and and I think
when something goes wrong it will it'll
have two meaningful outcomes one is
it'll get put right immediately the bot
will like escalate raise an issue issue
a refund
res yeah everything that's that needs
the Bott will also ship you a c Sal at
the end and like hey guy how did they do
Ry five out of five whatever the bot
will probably also do like an outcome
report on the back end and be like guys
t-shirt didn't arrive here's all the
chain of events that happened we think
it's because we used this provider in
the Middle East we think the day didn't
ship on time because they blah it'll do
what's the word like a postmortal almost
in every incident so I just think like
software and systems will get
dramatically better now the like the
question is what's the rest of the world
look like around all that because you
know and notably I think I think that's
a very compelling kind of reality and I
like it there's interesting questions on
it that we'll have to unravel in another
one but I guess the one question just to
ask on it is what's the role of a as a
support person in that world you
previously talked about how they elevate
into the sort of the bigger problems
does that
continue I think they control the
intelligence and they control the
policies so I think businesses will
still have to have opinions about what
type of customer service they want to
deliver what expectations they want to
set what what brand they want to project
but in 10 years time if you miss your
Riner flight I don't think AI is the
reason why ryer is going to be like no
worries we'll just put you on the next
one for free like I think that's an
actual business policy of ryer so like
somebody needs to tell the bot that
that's how the refund policy works if so
I think there'll be a master of policy a
master of intelligence of town of voice
of control perhaps safety harnesses too
like there probably will still be like
Escape switch for hello revolute I have
been hacked and all my money is draining
for my bank you probably don't want like
the chirpy bot replying to that one so I
think they'll be controlling the system
controlling the intelligence but I'm
also like I don't it's quite possible
that like that the the future support
team is like 10% to size of the current
ones we see today and that's just part
of the evolution of Technology yeah yeah
I think it's very interesting to think
about the roles that that form and the
power of them to an extent the more
power you have could be that there's 10
times as many services on it so the same
people in the world and just fewer of
them in every organization absolutely
yeah thanks for coming on and sharing
ing kind of these perspectives on on AI
tools and how they change development
and support and yeah I can't wait to see
how Finn continues to evolve and solve
all of our problems in all of the
vendors that we use cool same with El
thank you very much for having me it's
been fun chat cool and thanks everybody
for tuning in and I hope you join us for
the next one
[Applause]
thanks for tuning in join us next time
on the AI native Dev brought to you by
Tesla
[Music]